let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "True or False: Wasting less food is a way to reduce greenhouse gas emissions.",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "It could",
      "there is a small chance"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the Greenhouse effect?",
    answer: "When the gases in our atmosphere trap heat and block it from escaping our planet",
    options: [
      "The name of climate change legislation that was passed by Congress",
      "When you paint your house green to become an environmentalist",
      "When the gases in our atmosphere trap heat and block it from escaping our planet",
      "When you build a green house"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following are consequences associated with climate change?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Global sea levels are rising at an alarmingly fast rate — 17 centimeters (6.7 inches) in the last century alone and going higher",
      "The ice sheets are declining, glaciers are in retreat globally, and our oceans are more acidic than ever",
      "Surface temperatures are setting new heat records about each year",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What can you do to help fight climate change?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Divest from fossil fuel companies",
      "Vote for political candidates who will advocate for climate-related legislation and policy improvements",
      "Engage yourself in the science behind climate change",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What was agreed to in the 'Paris Agreement' that came out of COP-21, held in Paris in 2015?",
    answer: "To keep global temperature rise well below 2℃ pre-industrial levels and to pursue a path to limit warming to 1.5℃",
    options: [
      "To protect biodiversity and end the deforestation of the world’s rainforests",
      "To keep global temperature rise well below 2℃ pre-industrial levels and to pursue a path to limit warming to 1.5℃",
      "To limit sea level rise to 3 feet above current levels",
      "To pursue a goal of 100% clean, renewable energy"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of these countries emits the most carbon dioxide?",
    answer: "CHINA",
    options: [
      "USA",
      "UK",
      "CHINA",
      "RUSSIA"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What percentage of the global greenhouse gas emissions does the transportation sector emit?",
    answer: "14%",
    options: [
      "14%",
      "70",
      "33%",
      "1%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Choose the sentence which is in the present perfect tense:",
    answer: "She has just eaten her dinner.",
    options: [
      "They had already left the school.",
      "She will have finished her task.",
      "They would have called the boys.",
      "She has just eaten her dinner."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Globally, which of the following economic sectors emits the largest percentage of greenhouse gas emissions?",
    answer: "Electricity and heat production",
    options: [
      "Transportation",
      "Industry",
      "Buildings",
      "Electricity and heat production"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which five-year period was the warmest on record?",
    answer: "2016-2020",
    options: [
      "2001-2005",
      "2006-2010",
      "2011-2015",
      "2016-2020"
    ]
  }
];  